artipot.com 2015-03-17

# Artipot Privacy Policy

June 3, 2009

At Artipot we take your privacy seriously. This policy covers how Artipot treats personal information that is collected and received when you interact with our site or use our services.

**Information Collection and Use**

When you sign up for an [Author Account](http://authors.artipot.com/), we ask you for personal information (such as your name and email address). For certain services, such as our Email Article service, we also request certain personal information. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence in order to respond to your requests and to provide better service in the event you contact us again.

Artipot automatically records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Artipot cookie information, and the page you request.

Artipot uses information for the following general purposes: to provide our products and services to you, customize the advertising and content you see, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Artipot does not sell, trade, or rent personal information about you with other non-affiliated companies or individuals except under the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your permission.
  * We provide the information to trusted partners for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

**Cookies**

Artipot uses cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. However, some Artipot features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Third-Party Ad Networks**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Confidentiality and Security**

We restrict access to personal information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate or improve our services. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access, use or disclosure of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Artipot may update this policy from time to time. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this page and, if the changes are significant, a prominent notice will placed on our site. Your continued use of this site after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the modified privacy policy.
